<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IBS NeuroAI Group</title><link>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on IBS NeuroAI Group</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>News</title><link>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/news/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="news"&gt;
 News
 &lt;a class="heading-link" href="#news"&gt;
 &lt;i class="fa-solid fa-link" aria-hidden="true" title="Link to heading"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
 &lt;span class="sr-only"&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Multiple &lt;a href="https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/opportunities/" &gt;Openings&lt;/a&gt; for Research Positions!*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
 &lt;thead&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
 &lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;/thead&gt;
 &lt;tbody&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;12/16/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Three interns, Nayeon Kim, Jiseok Ryu, and Jinwoo Jung joined the group.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;12/16/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;New &lt;a href="https://ibs-neuroai-group.github.io/" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;lab website&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;11/24/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Our &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1101/2024.05.30.596563" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; on the neuro-glia interactions in the cerebellum is accepted in &lt;em&gt;Experimental &amp;amp; Molecular Medicine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;08/26/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Sungho organized a symposium &lt;em&gt;Neuroscience-inspired AI: Computational insights into biological and artificial intelligence&lt;/em&gt; at the KSBNS 2025 meeting.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;07/18/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Jisub&amp;rsquo;s poster won the best poster award at the Korean Computational Neuroscience Society (CBrain) 2025 meeting.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;07/01/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Two interns, Nayeon Kim and Sunwoo Choi join the group.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;02/11/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Sungho gave a lecture at the Computational Neuroscience Winter School 2025 organized by the Korean Computational Neuroscience Society (CBrain).&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;01/01/2025&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Oliver James and Jisub Bae join the group as Senior and Postdoctoral Researchers, respectively.&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;04/01/2024&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;td&gt;Lab opens!&lt;/td&gt;
 &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</description></item><item><title>Oliver James</title><link>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/people/oliver_james/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/people/oliver_james/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Oliver James is a Senior Researcher at the Center for Memory and Glioscience (CMG), IBS. Prior to joining CMG in 2022, he had been a Research Fellow at the Center for Neuroimaging Research, IBS-Sungkyunkwan University (2015-2022) and Postdoctoral Researcher at the School of Information and Communications, Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology (GIST) (2011-2015). He got a PhD in Singal Processing from the Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Madras in 2011, based on his work on the OFDM systems. His current research work combines computational modeling and signal processing to gain mechanistic insights into the brain function.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Sungho Hong</title><link>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/people/sungho_hong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibs-neuroai-lab.github.io/people/sungho_hong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Sungho Hong is a Senior Research Fellow in the Center for Memory and Glioscience at Institute for Basic Science (IBS) and the Principal Investigator of the Neuroscience-inspired AI group. He is also an Adjunct Professor in the &lt;a href="https://bme.unist.ac..kr" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Department of Biomedical Engineering&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href="https://www.unist.ac.kr" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)&lt;/a&gt;. Before joining IBS in 2024, he served as a Postdoctoral Researcher (2007–2012) and Group Leader (2012–2024) in the &lt;a href="https://www.oist.jp/research/research-units/cnu" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Computational Neuroscience Unit&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href="https://www.oist.jp" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Okinawa Institute of Science and Technology&lt;/a&gt;, Japan. Previously, he was a Senior Fellow in the &lt;a href="https://nbio.uw.edu" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Department of Physiology and Biophysics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.uw.edu" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;University of Washington&lt;/a&gt;, USA, during 2004–2007. He is a theoretical physicist by training and received his PhD in Physics from &lt;a href="https://www.upenn.edu" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;University of Pennsylvania&lt;/a&gt; in 2004. His research interests, broadly speaking, lie in uncovering biophysical underpinnings of computations performed by neural systems. He has been conducting computational modeling studies in collaboration with experimental neuroscientists to work on various topics ranging from single neuron computation to circuit-level mechanisms for circadian rhythm and cerebellum-dependent sensorimotor learning. His current research explores the interface between neuroscience and artificial intelligence (AI) research, focusing on the cerebellum and its interactions with other brain regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>